[
    {
        "prompt" : "The age that a person begins to develop a self-concept or self awareness is:",
        "correctAnswer" : "School-age",
        "answerList" : ["Preschool-age",
                        "Infant",
                        "School-age",
                        "Toddler"]
    },
    {
        "prompt" : "The age group that begins to start exploring their world, develops attachment to parents, and can resolve simple problems is:",
        "correctAnswer" : "Toddlers",
        "answerList" : ["Infants",
                        "Adolescents",
                        "Toddlers",
                        "School-age children"]
    },
    {
        "prompt" : "Early adulthood is:",
        "correctAnswer" : "The stage of development between 20 and 40 years old",
        "answerList" : [
                            "The stage of development between 15 and 30 years old", 
                            "The stage of development between 20 and 40 years old", 
                            "The stage of development between 10 and 20 years old", 
                            "The stage of development between 30 and 60 years old"
                        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt" : "Which of the following are characteristics of late adulthood?",
        "correctAnswer" : "Lung elasticity is diminished, pain perception is diminished, and metabolism is decreased.",
        "answerList" : [
                            "Lung elasticity is diminished, pain perception is diminished, and metabolism is decreased.", 
                            "Lung elasticity is diminished, insulin production increases, and the sleep cycle is disrupted.", 
                            "Workload and size of the heart increases, pain perception decreases and the sleep cycle is disrupted.", 
                            "Irregular sleep patterns develop, pain perception is increased, and metabolism is increased."
                        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt" : "A preschooler is:",
        "correctAnswer" : "3 - 6 years of age",
        "answerList" : [
                            "3 - 6 years of age", 
                            "1 - 12 months of age", 
                            "12 - 36 months of age"
                        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt" : "Menopause typically begins affecting a woman around:",
        "correctAnswer" : "Late 40s or 50s",
        "answerList" : [
                            "Late 40s or 50s", 
                            "Late 50s or 60s", 
                            "A broad time frame: it can vary widely, depending on the patient", 
                            "Late 30s or 40s"
                        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt" : "The age that most people reach peak physical condition is:",
        "correctAnswer" : "The early part of early adulthood",
        "answerList" : [
                            "Middle adulthood", 
                            "The late part of early adulthood", 
                            "The early part of early adulthood", 
                            "The late part of adolescence"
                        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt" : "Which of the following patients would have a normal respiratory rate between 20 and 30 breaths a minute?",
        "correctAnswer" : "Early adults",
        "answerList" : [
                            "Early adults", 
                            "School-age children", 
                            "Infants", 
                            "Adolescents"
                        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt" : "A toddler is:",
        "correctAnswer" : "12 - 36 months of age",
        "answerList" : [
                            "3 - 6 years of age", 
                            "1 - 12 months of age", 
                            "12 - 36 months of age" 
                        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt" : "A child that is 3 years old should at least be able to:",
        "correctAnswer" : "Walk alone and begin to run.",
        "answerList" : [
                            "Walk alone and begin to run.", 
                            "Stand one-legged for 10 seconds.", 
                            "Hop, jump, climb and do a somersault.",
                            "Dress himself." 
                        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt" : "By the age of 2 months, an infant should be able to:",
        "correctAnswer" : "Recognize faces and focus on things near to him",
        "answerList" : [
                            "Crawl and creep on his hands and knees", 
                            "Sit on his own", 
                            "Recognize faces and focus on things near to him",
                            "Pull himself up on furniture"
                        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt" : "Early adulthood is characterized by:",
        "correctAnswer" : "Fewer psychological problems than other age groups",
        "answerList" : [
                            "More psychological problems than other age groups", 
                            "Different types of psychological problems than other age groups", 
                            "Fewer psychological problems than other age groups" 
                        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt" : "An infant is:",
        "correctAnswer" : "1 - 12 months of age",
        "answerList" : [
                            "3 - 6 years of age", 
                            "1 - 12 months of age", 
                            "12 - 36 months of age" 
                        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt" : "Fontanelles can be used as a tool for diagnostics in any of the following ways, EXCEPT:",
        "correctAnswer" : "Palpate them to assess if there is a cranial fracture.",
        "answerList" : [
                            "Palpation will tell you if a child's brain is swelling or pushing up on the fontenelles.", 
                            "In suspected trauma, you can visualize if they are bulging and possibly indicate a swelling brain.", 
                            "Visualizing sunken in fontenelles will alert the EMT that the baby is dehydrated.",
                            "Palpate them to assess if there is a cranial fracture."
                        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt" : "One major difference between an infant an an adult is that:",
        "correctAnswer" : "The infant's lung tissue can easily rupture due to excessive ventilation pressure.",
        "answerList" : [
                            "The infant's lung tissue can easily rupture due to excessive ventilation pressure.", 
                            "Alveoli are greater with increased collateral ventilation.", 
                            "The infant's head is equal to 40% of its body weight.",
                            "You cannot assess mental status in an infant."
                        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt" : "In which of the following age groups are depression and suicide most common?",
        "correctAnswer" : "Adolescence",
        "answerList" : [
                            "Middle adulthood", 
                            "Adolescence", 
                            "Early adulthood",
                            "Late adulthood" 
                        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt" : "All of the following are ways to assess mental status in an infant EXCEPT:",
        "correctAnswer" : "If the infant is sleeping, he is most likely fine, since an infant would not sleep if he were ill",
        "answerList" : [
                            "Observing if an infant tracks you as you move around it", 
                            "If the infant is sleeping, he is most likely fine, since an infant would not sleep if he were ill", 
                            "Playing with toys",
                            "A loud active cry" 
                        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt" : "A child is no longer considered a neonate:",
        "correctAnswer" : "when he reaches 1 month of age.",
        "answerList" : [
                            "when he reaches 1 month of age.", 
                            "when he becomes a toddler.", 
                            "when he can sit up independently.",
                            "when he leaves the hospital." 
                        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt" : "Fontanelles:",
        "correctAnswer" : "Close between 3 months for the anterior and 9 to 18 months for the posterior.",
        "answerList" : [
                            "Close between 9 months for the anterior and 18 to 24 months for the posterior.", 
                            "Close between 12 months for the anterior and 24 to 36 months for the posterior.", 
                            "Close between 3 months for the anterior and 9 to 18 months for the posterior.",
                            "Close between 18 months for the anterior and 28 to 36 months for the posterior." 
                        ]
    },
    {
        "prompt" : "Which of the following patients would have a normal respiratory rate between 30 and 40 breaths a minute?",
        "correctAnswer" : "Toddlers",
        "answerList" : [
                            "Early adults", 
                            "Late adults", 
                            "Toddlers",
                            "Adolescents" 
                        ]
    }
]